▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 第三轮
斯瓦泰克 4-6 6-1 6-1 萨卡里 · 赛后场上采访
And in just under two hours,
两个小时不到
it ends with another Sakkari unforced error
萨卡里又一次非受迫失误
into the net.
球下网
Wasn't vintage Iga today.
今天不是巅峰状态的斯瓦泰克
Didn't get a break point even in the first set
首盘她一个破发点都没拿到
for the first time this season.
本赛季第一次
But how she came back, not spectacular,
但她扳回来的方式 算不上华丽
but very reliable and very consistent,
却非常可靠 非常稳定
dropping just two games,
只丢了两局
one in each of the second and third sets.
第二盘和第三盘各一局
Comes through it 6-1 in the third.
决胜盘六比一过关
The defending champion safely
卫冕冠军稳稳
through to the last 16.
打进 1/8 决赛
How important it is in this kind of weather.
这样的天气里 这一点太重要了
Iga, let's talk a little bit about the match.
斯瓦泰克 我们聊聊这场比赛
You turn things around today.
你今天把局面扭了过来
Let's take you right after the first set.
回到第一盘刚结束那会儿
How did you turn things around today?
你今天是怎么扭过来的？
It's hard to analyze it.
这很难分析
Honestly, I felt like I
说实话 我觉得自己
was playing quite good in a first set.
第一盘打得挺好
Sometimes just lacked maybe precision,
只是有时候差了点精准度
played too much to Maria
太多球送到了萨卡里手上
and she used the opportunities
她抓住了这些机会
and was playing, you know,
而且她的球
faster than me I felt like or deeper,
我感觉比我更快 或者更深
you know.
就是那种感觉
So I really wanted
所以我很想
to start pushing her so she doesn't get
开始压制她 别让她
so many opportunities
拿到那么多机会
to you know push me.
反过来压制我
So I'm happy
所以我很高兴
that in a second set it started working
第二盘开始奏效了
and I played a bit better.
我也打得好了一些
She started making mistakes
她开始出现失误
and I knew you know
我就知道
the momentum changed a little bit
势头有了一点变化
and now it's time to push.
该发力了
You flipped a switch that's for sure.
你确实像按了个开关
You've been very vocal lately
你最近常常谈到
about balancing life off the court
怎么平衡场外的生活
on the court.
和场上的自己
You seem like you're in such a good place
你现在的状态看起来非常好
and I think Cincinnati might have a lot
我想辛辛那提
to do with that.
和这有很大关系
The fans, they see you.
球迷们看见你
You walk out on court.
你走上球场
There's a lot of love for you here in Mason,
在梅森这里 大家非常喜欢你
Ohio.
俄亥俄州
What kind of place does that put you
这会让你
in mentally when you walk out
走上这样一片球场时
on a court like this?
心里是什么状态？
Well, this year,
今年
not much time to spend, you know,
没有太多时间
off the court cuz we came here pretty late.
待在场外 因为我们来得挺晚
But I'm happy, you know, that tomorrow
但我很高兴 明天
might have some time to just chill.
也许能有点时间放松
And Cincinnati for sure is a place to do that.
辛辛那提绝对适合做这件事
And yeah,
是啊
maybe we'll go eat some good food.
也许我们会去吃点好吃的
And thank you guys for being so welcoming
谢谢你们这么热情
and being so nice
这么友好
because this is the big part
因为这正是这项赛事
of this tournament, you know,
很重要的一部分
the atmosphere.
这里的氛围
So, I'm really happy to be here
所以我真的很高兴能在这里
for next days.
待上接下来几天
Well, we love having you here.
我们也很高兴你在这里
Well done, ladies and gentlemen.
打得漂亮 女士们先生们
Iga Swiatek.
斯瓦泰克